{
  "response": [
    {
      "question": "Docker was developed in",
      "option1": "2012",
      "option2": "2013",
      "option3": "2014",
      "option4": "2015",
      "answer": "2013"
    },
    {
      "question": "Command used for stopping a running container",
      "option1": "docker kill",
      "option2": "docker rm",
      "option3": "docker stop",
      "option4": "docker start",
      "answer": "docker kill"
    },
    {
      "question": " A docker registry is a place to store and distribute docker",
      "option1": "Images",
      "option2": "Codes",
      "option3": "Files",
      "option4": "All of the above",
      "answer": "Images"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does Kubernetes use Docker",
      "option1": "Yes",
      "option2": "No",
      "option3": "-",
      "option4": "-",
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "Is docker image OS Dependent",
     "option1": "Yes",
      "option2": "No",
      "option3": "-",
      "option4": "-",
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is the native clustering for Docker",
      "option1":  "Docker Hub",
      "option2":  "Docker Swarm",
      "option3":  "Docker Cloud",
      "option4": "Docker Compose",
      "answer": "Docker Swarm"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Docker Registry",
      "option1":  "Storage",
      "option2":  "Content Delivery System",
      "option3":  "Both of the Above",
      "option4": "None of the Above",
      "answer": "Both of the Above"
    },
    {
      "question": "You can't create multiple containers from the same image in Docker",
      "option1":  "True",
      "option2":  "False",
      "option3":  "-",
      "option4": "-",
      "answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "question": "Can we reomve a paused container from Docker",
      "option1": "Yes",
      "option2":"No",
      "option3": "-",
      "option4":"-",
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "___________ are instances of Docker images that can be run using the Docker run command.",
       "option1": "Hub",
      "option2": "Cloud",
      "option3": "File",
      "option4": "Container",
      "answer": "Container"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which command/s lists docker images?",
      "option1":  "Both docker images and docker images ls",
      "option2":  "docker images ls",
      "option3":  "docker images",
      "option4": "docker -i",
      "answer":  "Both docker images and docker images ls"
    },
    {
      "question": "Components of docker architecture is/are",
      "option1":  "docker-host",
      "option2": "docker-registry",
      "option3":"docker client",
      "option4":  "All of these",
      "answer": "All of these"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of these is shared by all the docker containers",
      "option1":  "Libraries",
      "option2": "Application",
      "option3":"Kernel",
      "option4":  "Operating System Software",
      "answer": "Kernel"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which commands shows number of images and containers",
     "option1":  "docker info",
      "option2":  "docker kill",
      "option3":  "docker prune",
      "option4": "docker network",
      "answer":  "docker info"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which orchestration tool handles multiple docker containers across different host machines",
     "option1":  "Both Docker Swarm and Kubernetes",
      "option2":  "Docker Swarm",
      "option3":  "Kubernetes",
      "option4": "None of the above",
      "answer":  "Both Docker Swarm and Kubernetes"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is/are Container orchestration technology",
     "option1":  "Mesos",
     "option2":  "Docker Swarm",
      "option3":  "Kubernetes",
      "option4": "All of the above",
      "answer":  "All of the above"
    },
    {
      "question": "________is a tool for defining and running multi-container Docker applications",
      "option1":  "Docker Hub",
      "option2":  "Docker Swarm",
      "option3":  "Docker Cloud",
      "option4": "Docker Compose",
      "answer": "Docker Compose"
    }
  ]
}